Finding Aid for the Peter H. Prince Papers MS.2921
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Publications, 1890-2005; II
  - Ghost Towns of the Great Smokies, 1892-2005; B
    - T: Willa Mae Trull, 2002 November 18 (Box 50, Folder 48)
    - T: University of Tennessee Libraries, 1988-1995 (Box 50, Folder 49)
    - U: University of North Carolina, Asheville, 1996-2005 (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - U: University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 51)
    - U: University of North Carolina Press, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 52)
    - U: United States Social Security, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 53)
    - U: University of Tennessee Press, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 54)
    - U: United States Geological Survey, undated (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - U: United States Geographic Board, 1993 June 3 (Box 50, Folder 56)
    - V: Veterans' Administration, 1996 April 17 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - V: Veterans Administration Regional Office, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 58)
    - V: Vanderbilt University E-Mail Account, 2002-2005 (Box 50, Folder 59)
    - V: Sam Venable, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 60)
    - V: Georgiana Fry Vines, 2005-2005 (Box 50, Folder 61)
    - V: Bert Vincent, Strolling, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 62)
    - V: Library of Virginia, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 63)
    - V: Vital Records (Tennessee) Forms, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - W: Hiram C. Wilburn, 1945-2000 (Box 50, Folder 65)
    - W: Bayard Wooten, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - W: Eugene Leslie Webb, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - W: Waterfalls, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - W: Western Carolina University, 1993-1997 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - W: Vic Weals (author), undated (Box 50, Folder 70)
    - W: Waynesville Interviews, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - W: Wears Valley Interviews, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Y: Maisie Queen Young, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 73)
  - Drafts, 1944-2003 (bulk 1987-2003); C
    - Footprints in the Great Smoky Mountains, 1995 January 21 (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - Ghost Towns Book Work Sheets, 1944, 1987-1996 (Box 50, Folder 75)
    - Ghost Towns Cover Designs, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Ghost Towns: Complete Draft, North Carolina Hazel Creek Pioneers (Volume I), 2003; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Ghost Towns: Complete Draft, Cataloochee/Mount Sterling (Volume II), undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - Ghost Towns: Complete Draft, Forney's Creek/Cherokee Removal (Volume III), 1995-1997; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk); [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 97, Folder 8] (Box 50, Folder 79)
    - Draft of Forney's Creek Township, 1995-1996; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Ghost Towns: Pictures and Descriptions for Volume II, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Ghost Towns: Complete Draft of Charleston Township (Volume III), 1996; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Ghost Towns: Complete Draft, Ocona Lufty Township (Volume IV), 1996; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Ghost Towns: Complete Draft, Ocona Lufty Township (Volume IV) (Edited by Maisie Queen Young), 1996; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Pete Prince Business Cards, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Draft, Big Abrams Gap, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Draft, Granville Calhoun (blank), undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Draft, James Calhoun Electrocuted, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Draft, Carolina & Tennessee Southern Railroad, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Cataloochee Township, Chilhowee, Foothills, Cades Cove, Wear, and Gatlinburg (most files unreadable), 1998; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Churches and Religion in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 2003 February 23; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Draft, Dalton Branch Logging Camp, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Draft, Dalton Gap, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Draft, Deals Gap, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Draft, Derrick Knob, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Draft, De Soto Visits Smokies, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Draft, Drill Cove, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Draft, Dynamite Train, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Draft, Emerts Cove and Jones Cove, 1991-1996; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Draft, Fontana Copper Mines, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Letter, Forney's Creek Parkway, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Draft, Forney Township, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Draft, Forrester Ridge, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Draft, Gatlinburg and Forney's Creek and Notes on Friends and AOL, 1997; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Draft, Gee, North Carolina, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Draft, Gregory's Bald, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Draft, Hall Herders Cabin, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Draft, Haw Gap, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Draft, Hazel Creek CCC Camp 2453 (blank), 2002; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Draft, Hazel Creek Cascades, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Fort Harry Drafts and Articles, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Draft, Jenkins Trail Ridge, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Draft, Kitchen Logging Camp, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Draft, Medlin, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Caption, Monteith Family Photograph, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Draft, Moore Springs, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Articles, Announcements, and Drafts for Oconaluftee and Knoxville Night Time, 1995; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Draft, Parson Bald, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Draft, Proctor Field Gap, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Railroad Letters and Articles, 2003; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Draft, Rocky Point Ferry, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Draft, Thad Sherrill Lynching, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Draft, Spruce Flats Falls, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Draft, Stikeleather Cabin, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Notes and Captions for Swain County, Squires, Townsend, Walland, and Wears, 1996-2003; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Draft, Tennessee River and Tennessee River Road, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Notes, Andres Thompson Genealogy, 1996 November 5; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Draft, Twentymile Creek, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Draft, Upper Flats Camp, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - E-Mail, US 129 Dowsing Trip, 2002 September 30; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Draft, Whiting Ferry, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - Draft, Woodward Knob, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Draft,Woody, North Carolina, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Indices (blank) to Forney's Creek Township and Hazel Creek and Descriptions of Prince Research Files, 2002; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 55)
    - Ghost Towns Correspondence, 1991-1993; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - Ghost Towns Correspondence, 1995; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 57)
    - Book Writing Events, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - Notes on Book Sources, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Prince Overmountain Press, 2003 March; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 60)
    - Ghost Towns Hike Advertisement, undated; (Printed from 3.5 in. Floppy Disk) (Box 51, Folder 61)
    - Ghost Towns Floppy Disks, undated; [Disks Removed to Box 55] (Box 51, Folder 62)
- Personal Papers, 1980-2006; III
  - Cerebral Palsy Advocacy, 1997-2005; A
    - Sydney and Jordan Ashcraft, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 63)
    - Blount Memorial Hospital: Fifty Years of Caring Together, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 64)
    - Citizen Tribune, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 65)
    - Covenant Health, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 66)
    - Euromed Rehabilitation Center, undated (Box 51, Folder 67)
    - Euromed: Eric Smelcer's Therapy Fund, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 68)
    - Euromed: Pete Prince's Travel to Poland, 2003 May-June (Box 51, Folder 69)
    - Euromed: Richard Kowalczyk (General Director), 2003 (Box 51, Folder 70)
    - Euromed: General Information, 2003; (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 71)
    - Euromed: General Information, 2003; (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 72)
    - Euromed: Eric Smelcer Therapy, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 73)
    - Jefferson City, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 74)
    - Knoxville Cerebral Palsy Center, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 75)
    - Knoxville News-Sentinel, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 76)
    - Loose Materials, 2003-2005 (Box 51, Folder 77)
    - Maryville, undated (Box 51, Folder 78)
    - Sammy McKamey, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 79)
    - Morristown, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 80)
    - Mount Hope, USA, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 81)
    - The Mountain Press, undated (Box 51, Folder 82)
    - John Ogle, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 83)
    - Pittman Center, 2003 October 20 (Box 51, Folder 84)
    - Rotary International, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 85)
    - WBIR, undated (Box 51, Folder 86)
    - Beverly Woodruff, undated (Box 51, Folder 87)
    - WUOT Radio, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 51, Folder 88)
    - YMCA Camp Montvale, undated (Box 51, Folder 89)
    - Camp Montvale Photographs, undated (Box 51, Folder 90)
  - Housing, 1980-2005 (bulk 2002-2005); B
    - Garden Vale Apartments General File, 1994-2001 (Box 51, Folder 91)
    - Garden Vale Apartments HUD Violations, 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 92)
    - Garden Vale Photographs, circa 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 93)
    - Garden Vale Apartments, 2003 August 28 (Box 51, Folder 94)
    - West Nile Virus in Standing Garden Vale Pools?, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Garden Vale Denies that it Must Comply with Maryville City Codes, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Bob Jones (Juvenile Detention Officer), Double Parks, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Garden Vale Apartment vs. Pete Prince, 1994-2003 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Glen Nicely, 1980, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Legal Aid of East Tennessee/Eviction from Garden Vale, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Pete Prince Applies for Housing at Broadway Towers/Garden Vale Apartments vs. Pete Prince, 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Broadway Towers/Garden Vale, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Letter to John J. Duncan Jr., 2003 May 21 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Pete Prince Prepares Lawsuit, circa 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Broadway Towers Application, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Beverly Sherrod Fired at Broadway Towers, 2003 July (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 2003 November 24 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Habitat for Humanity Homeowner Training Class Literature, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Habitat for Humanity Selection and Work, 1996, 2003-2005 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Habitat for Humanity Sweat Equity Hours, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Habitat for Humanity Education and Work, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Blount County Habitat for Humanity vs. Pete Prince (Charged with Lying and Sexual Harassment), 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Deselection from Habitat for Humanity Program, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Habitat for Humanity Binder, undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Work at 128 West Bill Street, Alcoa, 2004 August 28 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Everette High Work, 2005 March 26 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Click House Work, 2004 May 13 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Women's Build at 622 Everette, 2005 March 26 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Sands House Dedication, 2005 February 26 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Habitat for Humanity: House Dedication Photographs, circa 2000s (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Home Dedication, 2005 May 8; (Negatives) (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Car Accident and Lawsuit, 2003-2006 (bulk 2004-2005); C
    - Accident Report and Alcoa Police Department, 2003-2005 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Damage to Automobile (Including Repair, Towing, and Rental), 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Photographs of Injuries, Damage to Car, and Defendants' Homes, circa 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Medical Progress Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Medical Expenses and Extent of Injuries, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Other Medical Information, 2004-2006; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 97, Folder 9] (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Lawsuit, Pete Prince v. Lisa G. Fields and Christopher M. Mills, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence with H. Allen Bray, Esq., 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Other Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Profile Sheets, 1992-2006; D
    - Church Street United Methodist Singles Group, 1993-2004 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Cokesbury United Methodist Singes, 1998-2003 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Friends of the South, 1988-2002 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Knoxville Country Dancers, Friends of the South, and Smoky Mountains Hiking Club, 1993-1997 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Knoxville Night Time, 1993-2003 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Rotary Club of Maryville, 1992-2006; (1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Rotary Club of Maryville, 1992-2006; (2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Singles Dinner Club of East Tennessee, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1993-2006; E
    - Church Street United Methodist's Bahamas Benefit Cruise, 1993 June 26-July 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Friends: Hutsell Descendants at Rotary Centennial Station, 2005 April 22; (Negatives) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Friends: Tammy Middleton, circa 2005 May (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Friends: Philippine Dinner at Rotary Pavilion, 2005 April 6 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Friends: Philippine Dinner at Rotary Pavilion, 2005 April 26 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Friends: Natasha Sulzhenko, 1993 May 6 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Georgia: Daisy, Millegeville, Meigs-Freeman Line, and Waters Family Graves, 2005 May 23-25 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Georgia: Savannah, LeConte Family Graves, Woodmanston Plantation, and Methodist Landmarks, 2005 May 21-23; [Caricatures removed to Box 97, Folder 10] (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Germany: Berlin/Iron Curtain, 2003 June (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Mexico (Cancun) and Monmouth, (New Jersey) Battlefield, circa 2003 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - North Carolina: Duke Chapel, Duke Gardens, and Sweetwater Creek, 2005 April 25-27 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - North Carolina: Cape Hatteras National Seashore, Oracoke Island, and Wright Brothers Monument, 2005 April 28 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - North Carolina: Terri Swaggert, 2002 July 28 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Optimist International Logo, undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Pete Prince and Aliese Griffin Hutsell, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Pete Prince and Berdine Herbert at Mardi Gras at Northgate Terrace, 2004 February 17 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Pete Prince's Birthday Dinner, 2001 June (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Poland: President Bush and Auschwitz, 2003 June (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Poland: Euromed, circa 2003 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Poland: European Scenes, 2003 June (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Poland: Warsaw, Baltic Sea, and Milano, 2003 June (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Smoky Mountains: Homes, Illegible Tombstones, and Scenery, 2004 May 10 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Smoky Mountains: Railroad Bridges, 2003 September 6 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Smoky Mountains: Scenery, Trails, and Markers, undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Smoky Mountains and South Carolina, circa 2000s (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Smoky Mountains: Tunnels, Railroads, Mills, and Signs, 2003 August 8 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Smoky Mountains: Jones Mountain, Max Patch, and Homes, 1998 January 13-14 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Tennessee: Return J. Meigs and Griffin Family Graves, 2005 June 13; (Negatives) (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Trip to Sterk's (?) Lodge (near Mount Cammerer), 1993 January 23 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Tombstones for David Hale, Ben Parton, John C. Higdon, and Pete Prince and Scenery, 2004 September 12-October 27 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Pete Prince's Tombstone, 2004 October 17-November 14 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Family, 2004 July 8 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Photographs, circa 2000s; (1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Photographs, circa 2000s; (2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Photographs, circa 2000s; (3 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified Images, circa 2000s; (Negatives) (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Other Papers, 1994-2006; F
    - Blank U. S. Census Forms, undated; (1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Blank U. S. Census Forms, undated; (2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Blank U. S. Census Forms, undated; (3 of 3) (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Blank Notepad, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Bookend, undated; [Removed to Box 56] (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Cariten Senior Health HMO Member Handbook and Provider Directory, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Church Street United Methodist Church Directory, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Pellissippi State Technical and Community College Catalog and Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Smoky Mountains Hiking Club Handbook, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Stamp Reading Photographs - Do Not Bend, undated; [Removed to Box 57] (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Oversized and Other Materials, 1833-2006; IV
  - Floppy Disks, undated; [Disks Removed from Box 51, Folder 62] (Box 55)
  - Bookend, undated; [Removed from Box 54, Folder 3] (Box 56)
  - Stamp Reading Photographs - Do Not Bend, undated; [Removed from Box 54, Folder 9] (Box 57)
  - Oversized Materials, 1823-2003 (Box 58)
  - Oversized Materials, 1770-2006 (Box 59)
  - Oversized Materials, 1837-2005 (Box 60)
  - Oversized Materials, 1832, 1860-2004 (Box 61)
  - Oversized Materials, 1872-2005 (Box 62)
  - Oversized Materials, 1874-2006 (Box 63)
  - Oversized Materials, 1872-2005 (Box 64)
  - Oversized Materials, 1888-2004 (Box 65)
  - Oversized Materials, 2000-2003 (Box 66)
  - Oversized Materials, 1908-1975 (Box 67)
  - Oversized Materials, circa 1910-1995 (Box 68)
  - Oversized Materials, 1904-1997 (Box 69)
  - Oversized Materials, circa 1899-2003 (Box 70)
  - Oversized Materials, 1905-2006 (Box 71)
  - Oversized Materials, 1900-1996 (Box 72)
  - Oversized Materials, 1896-2005 (Box 73)
  - Oversized Materials, 1884-2003 (Box 74)
  - Oversized Materials, 1912-1997 (Box 75)
  - Oversized Materials, 1897-1995 (Box 76)
  - Oversized Materials, 1937-1999 (Box 77)
  - Oversized Materials, 1996 September (Box 78)
  - Oversized Materials, 1896-1999 (Box 79)
  - Oversized Materials, 1914-1999 (Box 80)
  - Oversized Materials, 1867-1998 (Box 81)
  - Oversized Materials, 1898-1998 (Box 82)
  - Oversized Materials, 1926 (Box 83)
  - Oversized Materials, 1896-2005 (Box 84)
  - Oversized Materials, 1903-1992 (Box 85)
  - Oversized Materials, 1886-1910 (Box 86)
  - Oversized Materials, 1886-1961 (Box 87)
  - Oversized Materials, 1886-2005 (Box 88)
  - Oversized Materials, 1877-2001 (Box 89)
  - Oversized Materials, 1886-2006 (Box 90)
  - Oversized Materials, 1940 (Box 91)
  - Oversized Materials, 1940-1991 (Box 92)
  - Oversized Materials, 1884-2000 (Box 93)
  - Oversized Materials, 1833-2003 (Box 94)
  - Oversized Materials, 1870, 1987-2005 (Box 95)
  - Oversized Materials, 1890-2005 (Box 96)
  - Oversized Materials, 1892-2006 (Box 97)